http://www.pomics.com/privacy.html

Southern Cross Online Publishing Group Australia, recognises the importance of protecting the information collected from Users in the operation of this website, and takes all reasonable steps to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of any information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the Australian National Privacy Principles. By submitting your information to Southern Cross Publishing Group Australia you consent to the practices described herein.
Southern Cross Publishing Group Australia will ensure that any identifiable personal information it collects during the registration and any other processes will be adequate, relevant and not excessive for purposes of operating this website or any of the services operated hereunder, it will be kept accurate and up-to-date based on information provided and it will be deleted when no longer needed. Except where necessary in connection with services provided by appropriate intermediaries, who will be required to comply with the confidentiality provisions of this policy, Sothern Cross Publishing Group will not disclose any personal information identifying Users to any third party, unless required by law or otherwise needed in connection with legal proceedings or unless we have received your consent.   Southern Cross Publishing Group Australia protects the security of User Information by using an trustable encryption technology software.
Links may be provided from this website to other third party websites. In using such links, Users should be aware that each third party website will vary in terms of its privacy and data protection policies, and Southern Cross Publishing Group does not take responsibility for the privacy policies of, and usage of, personal information collected by others.
You should be aware that identifiable personal information--such as your name or e-mail address--that you voluntarily disclose that are accessible to others in the public domain (e.g. on bulletin boards or in chat areas) could be collected and disclosed by others. Southern Cross Publishing Group cannot take any responsibility for such collection and disclosure.
Please note that Southern Cross Publishing Group Australia's Privacy Policy is reviewed periodically. Southern Cross Publishing Group Australia reserves the right to modify its Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page. Your continued use of this website will be deemed conclusive acceptance of such modification. Any comments, questions or complaints concerning this policy should be addressed by entering your comments through our Contact Us page. If at any point you wish to access your personal information to (1) change your preferences, (2) review the accuracy, or (3) correct, supplement or modify your information, you may either  Contact Us via email.
Southern Cross Publishing Group Australia will not sell personal information for marketing purposes under any circumstances.
Information Quality
Southern Cross Publishing Group Australia will take all reasonable steps to ensure that personal information collected, used or disclosed is accurate, complete and up-to-date.
